// data/questions.js
const questions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "1. What is the capital of France?",
    options: [1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    unseen: true,
    attempted: false,
    pending: true,
    time: 0,
    type: "maths",
  },

  {
    id: 2,
    question: "2. who are you",
    options: [1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    unseen: true,
    attempted: false,
    pending: true,
    time: 0,
    type: "maths",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "3. Who painted the Mona Lisa?",
    options: [1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    unseen: true,
    attempted: false,
    pending: true,
    time: 0,
    type: "maths",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "4. What is the currency of Brazil?",
    options: [1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    unseen: true,
    attempted: false,
    pending: true,
    time: 0,
    type: "maths",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "5. What is the largest planet in our solar system?",
    options: [1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    unseen: true,
    attempted: false,
    pending: true,
    time: 0,
    type: "maths",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: '6. Who wrote the novel "Pride and Prejudice"?',
    options: [1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    unseen: true,
    attempted: false,
    pending: true,
    time: 0,
    type: "maths",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "7. In which city is the Eiffel Tower located?",
    options: [1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    unseen: true,
    attempted: false,
    pending: true,
    time: 0,
    type: "maths",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: '8. Which artist painted "Starry Night"?',
    options: [1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    unseen: true,
    attempted: false,
    pending: true,
    time: 0,
    type: "maths",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "9. What is the largest ocean in the world?",
    options: [1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    unseen: true,
    attempted: false,
    pending: true,
    time: 0,
    type: "upsc",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "10. Who discovered gravity?",
    options: [1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    unseen: true,
    attempted: false,
    pending: true,
    time: 0,
    type: "maths",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: "11. Which city hosted the 2016 Summer Olympics?",
    options: [1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    unseen: true,
    attempted: false,
    pending: true,
    time: 0,
    type: "maths",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: "12. Who painted the ceiling of the Sistine Chapel?",
    options: [1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    unseen: true,
    attempted: false,
    pending: true,
    time: 0,
    type: "maths",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: "13. What is the largest animal on Earth?",
    options: [1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    unseen: true,
    attempted: false,
    pending: true,
    time: 0,
    type: "maths",
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: "14. Which country is home to the Great Barrier Reef?",
    options: [1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    unseen: true,
    attempted: false,
    pending: true,
    time: 0,
    type: "maths",
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question: '15. Who is the author of "To Kill a Mockingbird"?',
    options: [1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    unseen: true,
    attempted: false,
    pending: true,
    time: 0,
    type: "maths",
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    question: "16. What is the capital of Canada?",
    options: [1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    unseen: true,
    attempted: false,
    pending: true,
    time: 0,
    type: "maths",
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    question: '17. Who painted the "Last Supper"?',
    options: [1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    unseen: true,
    attempted: false,
    pending: true,
    time: 0,
    type: "maths",
  },

  // Add more questions here
  {
    id: 18,
    question: "18. What is the capital of Canada?",
    options: [1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    unseen: true,
    attempted: false,
    pending: true,
    time: 0,
    type: "maths",
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    question: '19. Who painted the "Last Supper"?',
    options: [1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    unseen: true,
    attempted: false,
    pending: true,
    time: 0,
    type: "maths",
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    question: "20. What is the capital of Canada?",
    options: [1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    unseen: true,
    attempted: false,
    pending: true,
    time: 0,
    type: "maths",
  },
  {
    id: 21,
    question: '21. Who painted the "Last Supper"?',
    options: [1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    unseen: true,
    attempted: false,
    pending: true,
    time: 0,
    type: "maths",
  },
  {
    id: 22,
    question: "22. What is the capital of Canada?",
    options: [1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    unseen: true,
    attempted: false,
    pending: true,
    time: 0,
    type: "maths",
  },
  {
    id: 23,
    question: '23. Who painted the "Last Supper"?',
    options: [1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    unseen: true,
    attempted: false,
    pending: true,
    time: 0,
    type: "maths",
  },
  {
    id: 24,
    question: "24. What is the capital of Canada?",
    options: [1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    unseen: true,
    attempted: false,
    pending: true,
    time: 0,
    type: "maths",
  },
  {
    id: 25,
    question: '25. Who painted the "Last Supper"?',
    options: [1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    unseen: true,
    attempted: false,
    pending: true,
    time: 0,
    type: "maths",
  },
];

export default questions;
